{
    "subject": "resource/Magadan",
    "predicate": "property/postalCodes",
    "object": "685000",
    "human_readable": "The postal code of Magadan is 685000.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8935737013816833,
            "question": "Is 685000 a valid postal code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8681750893592834,
            "question": "What city has a postal code of 685000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8267898559570312,
            "question": "What is the postal code of Magadan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33878007531166077,
            "question": "How are postal codes used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27349284291267395,
            "question": "What information does a postal code provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2714993357658386,
            "question": "Are there different types of postal codes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23566831648349762,
            "question": "What is the purpose of using postal codes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1977127343416214,
            "question": "In which country is Magadan located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19206608831882477,
            "question": "Can you give an example of another city and its postal code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12254277616739273,
            "question": "How does a postal code help with mail delivery?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The postal code of Magadan is 685000.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1843_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of another city and its postal code?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1843_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country is Magadan located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1843_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the purpose of using postal codes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1843_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1843_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple documents that mention the city or town of Magadan and its postal code, which is consistently stated to be 685000. For example, in document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1843/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt, it says \"POSTAL ADDRESS 685000, MAGADAN...\". Similarly, in document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1843/re-ranker-msmarco/73.txt, it mentions an \"Interactive map of zip codes in Magadan, Russia\" and lists the postal code as 685000."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the document `73.txt`, which includes a search interactive map for zip codes in Magadan, Russia, confirming that the postal code of Magadan is indeed 685000."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}